어떤 나라에서는 하객들이 침실밖에서
In some cultures, we'd stand outside of their bedroom
부부가 오르가즘에 오르면 같이 환호를 해준대
cheering as they achieved orgasm.
나도 참석하고 싶지만
That sounds like a late night,
내일 일이 있어서...
and I have work in the morning, so...
레너드, 모르는가 본데
Leonard, you may not have noticed,
난 널 기쁘게 하려고 지금 애쓰고 있어
but I am being a delight here.
그런데 너는 별로 시원찮은 반응이다
And you're not holding up your end of the evening.
미안해. 결혼식에 오니까
Oh, sorry. This wedding just reminds me
이역만리에 떨어져 있는 내 여자친구가 생각나서
of my kinda-sorta girlfriend 9,000 miles away.
나도 남자친구가 장난감 기차에 미쳐있는데
I have a kinda-sorta boyfriend who's playing with a model train
내가 한 번이라도 지랄하는거 들어봤냐
right now, you don't hear me bitching about it.